本人  克莱尔·黑尔·安德伍德
I, Claire Hale Underwood,
在此庄严宣誓
do solemnly swear
我必忠实执行
that I will faithfully execute the office
合众国总统职务
of President of the United States...
我真为她骄傲  这是她应得的
I'm proud of her. She deserves this.
哪怕只能当几个星期
Even if it only lasts for a couple of weeks.
忠于职守  竭尽全力
And will, to the best of my ability,
恪守  维护和捍卫
preserve, protect, and defend
合众国宪法  愿上帝助我
the Constitution of the United States, so help me God.
恭喜你  代总统女士
Congratulations, Madam Acting President.
人人影视倾情奉献
翻译   国士章鱼X
翻译   咖喱味的虚寒
翻译   PiPi
翻译   杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译   吃冰棒
翻译   WalkingNerd
翻译   煮粥
时间轴   壬虚浪影
时间轴   噃噃
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
校对   草草
总监   草草
纸牌屋
第五季  第六集
-感觉有什么不一样吗  -没有
- Feel different? - No.
-骗我  -暂时而已  我只是代总统
- Liar. - It's temporary. I'm only acting.
现在你得全天候随身带着这个了
You have to now carry this with you at all times.
-密码吗  -没错  法律规定的
- The codes? - Mmm- hmm. It's the law.
州长  我们刚刚听说
Governor, we just got word
副总统克莱尔·安德伍德
that Vice President Claire Underwood
已宣誓就任代总统
was sworn in as acting president.
您知道吗
Were you aware?
我当然知道
Of course.
您有什么评论吗
Do you have any comment?
上帝保佑美国
God bless America.
如果众议院周一的投票选了您
If Monday's House vote goes your way,
-您成功当选的话  -我会赢的  相信我
- and you win the presidency... - Oh, I'll win, believe me.
您觉得这第三次投票能让您当选
You think this vote will be the charm?
国会和全国人民心情是一样的
See, Congress is no different than the rest of the country.
人民厌倦了这种政坛乱局和纷争
People are sick and tired of all this confusion and chaos.
公众非常不满
The public is not happy.
如果您当选总统
If you become president,
克莱尔·安德伍德还会继续担任副总统吗
would Claire Underwood remain as vice president?
如果她为国家大局着想的话  就不会
Not if she wants what's best for the country.
可是第十二修正案有明文规定  你有的选吗
But given the Twelfth Amendment, would you have a choice?
大家就问到这里吧
Uh, no further questions, everybody.
州长还要和国会议员们会面
The governor's here to talk to members of Congress.
非常感谢各位  谢谢
Thank you so much. Thank you.
谢谢  谢谢大家
Thank you. Thanks, everybody.
-威尔  -我没事
- Will? - I'm fine.
拉斯姆森也改立场了
And Rasmussen changed his vote.
他一直想找机会报复我
Well, he's been waiting a long time to pay me back.
在罗德岛搞出个僵局好让他博得关注
Creating a deadlock in Rhode Island just gives him the spotlight.
-可以说服他  -会议定在今天下午
- He can be convinced. - Meeting's set for this afternoon.
可如果说服不了他  我们就失去罗德岛了
Yes, but if we can't, we lose Rhode Island.
他似乎是一个人  但也可能有别人支持他
He seems to be acting alone, but that could change.
这个周末我们会取得进展的
We will make gains this weekend.
在周一投票前稳住局面
Shore things up by Monday's vote.
总统先生
Mr. President,
我们可能需要考虑另一种选项
it's possible we may need to consider the other option.
改期重新大选
A rescheduled election.
不  我会让拉斯姆森乖乖的
No, no, I'll get Rasmussen back in line,
顺便再多拉几票过来
and turn some others along the way.
我们已经为你和总统女士安排了
We've arranged sit-downs for you and Madam President
和各小州议员的会面
with all of the small states.
莉安和我可以去雷伯恩  朗沃斯和加农
LeAnn and I can go door-to-door in Rayburn,
三栋众议院办公楼逐门拜访
Longworth and Cannon.
除了白宫  我最喜欢这三栋楼了
Three of my favorite buildings after this one.
什么事
What is it?
南极洲麦克默多研究站
The McMurdo Research Facility in Antarctica.
所有实时通讯渠道都中断下线了
All live feed communications have ceased or been disconnected.
不过我们收到了一名驻站的
However, we have been receiving texts and e-mails
美国科考人员的短信和电邮
from an American scientist stationed there,
说有身份不明的
claiming that an unidentified
武装人员实施了登陆占领
occupying military force has landed.
你认为这些士兵是俄军吗
You think the soldiers are Russian?
他这么认为
He thinks so.
他们乘坐的是无标记的科考船
They arrived via unmarked research vessels.
我们联系了莫斯科
We reached out to Moscow,
但他们否认与此事有任何官方联系
but they're denying any official involvement.
想不到啊
Surprise, surprise.
这就是悍然入侵
It's a brazen act of aggression.
他这是心存侥幸
Well, it's a crime of opportunity.
佩特罗夫认为美国政府现在无暇他顾
Petrov thinks the US government has their eye off the ball.
他想错了
Well, it doesn't.
凯茜  我们收到的最近一次通讯是什么
Cathy, what's the most recent communication we've received?
我是说  由不明力量发起的
What I'm saying is this aggression in Antarctica,
对南极洲的入侵
by powers unknown,
正是总统之位一事
is a direct result of the uncertainty
迟迟不得以解决造成的直接恶果
that our presidential situation has wrought.
沃茨众议员  国会黑人党团什么时候
Congressman Watts, since when is Antarctica a concern
开始这么关心南极洲的事了
for the Congressional Black Caucus?
我希望你不是在暗示
I hope you're not implying that the caucus
黑人党团无权就国际事务发表意见
shouldn't have a voice in international affairs.
我希望你不是这个意思  谢谢你  兰迪
I hope that's not what I'm hearing. Thank you, Randy.
我将于明天
I've called a meeting tomorrow,
召集国会黑人党团开会  在周一总统投票前
for the Congressional Black Caucus, to discuss our positions,
讨论本党团在国内外各项议题上的立场
both foreign and domestic, before Monday's presidential vote.
您是在考虑转而支持康威吗
Are you considering shifting your support to Conway?
我现在只能说
Well, all I can say at this time,
最重要的是团结
that the most important thing is unity...
以及民众对民主制度的信心
and the public's faith in the institution of democracy.
就这样
That's all for now.
你违反了《南极条约体系》
You are in violation of the Antarctic Treaty System.
那是苏联1959年签订的条约
A treaty the USSR signed in 1959.
我们已经是个新国家了
We're a new country.
所以你承认了那是你的军队
So you're admitting they are your troops.
我只是说我需要
I'm simply stating I need to
解释一下由苏联签订的协议
interpret agreements signed by the Soviet Union.
那么
In which case,
你就是否定了几十年来的裁军进程
you'd be throwing out decades of disarmament progress.
冷战已经结束了  代总统女士
The Cold War is over, Mrs. Acting President.
那我们也许需要重新修订条约
Well, then maybe we need to revisit the treaty.
我对那不感兴趣
I'm not interested in revisiting a treaty.
我只关心继续执政
I'm interested in staying in power.
克莱尔
And, Claire...
如果我能这样称呼你的话
if I could be so familiar.
在我的国家
In my country...
一旦你上了台  就不会放权
once you're in office, you don't let go.
-维克多  -总统先生
- Viktor. - Mr. President.
你们美国人现在的总统可真不少
You Americans certainly have a lot of presidents these days.
是啊  你可能觉得我们无暇他顾
Yes, you may think that we're distracted,
别骗自己了
but don't fool yourself.
无暇他顾  不不不
Distracted? No. No, no.
分裂才对
Divided, yes.
美国的民主制度可比你
American democracy is stronger than your
利用这种小麻烦的可悲企图强大
sad attempt to take advantage of a bump in the road.
弗兰西斯  我的关注范围
Oh, Francis, my eyes are on a landscape
可远大于你们任何人的前途
that is so much bigger than any one of your roads.
拉斯姆森议员
Well, Congressman Rasmussen,
我们只是惊讶你会
we're just surprised to see you come out
站错边  就这样
on the wrong end of this, is all.
我知道那么多年前
I mean, I suppose it must've been hard
丢掉了众议院多数党领袖的位子
losing the House majority leadership
一定很不好受
all those years ago,
但心怀怨愤
but there is a difference
和背叛之间还是有区别的
between being bitter and being treasonous.
如果你是想要新的委员会席位
If it's new committee assignments you'd like,
我们完全可以安排
we can certainly arrange that.
已经结束了
It's over.
市场一落千丈
Markets are in free fall.
消费者信心到了历史最低点
Consumer confidence is at an all-time low.
这是什么  装饰品  小玩意
What is this? A doodad? A doohickey?
还是什么没用的奖品
A... pointless award?
我有说过我讨厌没用的东西吗
Did I mention I hate useless things?
这个国家已经在崩溃了
This nation is coming apart at the seams.
是因为你  因为你对这个国家做的事
Because of you, because of what you've done to this country.
看吧
There it is.
正义人士总喜欢感慨他们自己中层管理者的角色
How the righteous love to bemoan their role in middle management,
而谴责那些真能影响世界的人
and condemn those who actually might have an effect on the world.
-考虑考虑党派利益  议员  -我考虑了
- Think of the party, Congressman. - I am.
你觉得你来这儿能怎么样  弗兰西斯
What did you think would happen when you came in here, Francis?
你能威胁我
That you could threaten me,
告诉我不合作的话  全国委员会下一轮选举
tell me the DNC'll throw money at my primary opponent next cycle
就把钱投给我的劲敌
if I don't play ball?
还是说你打算奉承我
Or were you gonna flatter me?
一会儿说我是"党内长老"
"Elder of the party" this,
一会儿说我是"资深成员领头羊"
"bellwether senior member" that.
我真有点高兴
You know, I'm somewhat delighted
你到了这把年纪还能发展出点个性
that you developed a personality at this late date.
但我希望你再想想
But I would ask you to rethink this.
在你职业生涯的晚期闹这样的事情
To come out this way on this thing in the twilight of your career
只会给你的维基百科添一笔污点
will do nothing but sully your Wikipedia page.
你根本不明白  是吧
You have no idea, do you?
你在这里没有分量了
No one hears you walking the halls of this building...
现在没有了
not anymore.
-你在帮谁做事  -什么
- Who are you working for? - Excuse me?
我跟你这个软骨头共事了二十年
I served next to your jellied spine for two decades.
你从没表现出过一点勇气
You've never shown an ounce of courage.
你没有复仇的本事
You don't have what it takes for revenge.
所以肯定有人给了你不少好处
So someone must have offered you something rather sweet.
好好重新考虑两小时吧
Take all of the two hours you need to reconsider.
还有一份需要您签字
One more thing for your signature.
克莱尔·安德伍德  美国代总统
特许安全权限
-放在这里就可以了  -好的
- You can leave this with me. - Of course.
弗兰西斯·安德伍德
-哈维女士在等您  -请让她进来
- And Miss Harvey's waiting. - Oh, please send her in.
我正要回雷伯恩大楼
I'm on my way back to Rayburn.
请关上门
You close the door, please?
重新投票我们获胜的可能性有多大
What are our chances with a revote?
或者说  总统获胜的可能性有多大
Or, rather, what are the president's chances?
我想知道
I want to know.
就全部50个州而言  情况不太好
If it was in all 50 states, not good.
他的反对率还是很高  而你依然低
His unfavorables are still high. Yours are still not.
但他有近30年的经验  所以也不好说
But it's hard to argue with close to 30 years' experience.
也许总统是对的
Maybe the president is right.
或许他确实在众议院那里把握更大
Maybe he does have a better chance in the House.
别绕弯子  莉安  告诉我你怎么想的
Don't defer, LeAnn. Tell me what you think.
田纳西和俄亥俄的重投是他的最佳机会
The revote in Tennessee and Ohio is his best shot.
这对弗兰克来说是最佳
While it's what's best for Frank,
可未必对你来说最佳
it may not be what's best for you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你似乎是个通情达理的人
You seem like a reasonable man.
我懂得倾听  你是指这个吗
I know how to listen, if that's what you mean.
如果总统重获职位
If the president regains his office--
一开口就是如果怎么行  艾力克斯
"If" doesn't make for a winning opener, Alex.
我来这里是因为我觉得他能赢
I'm here because I think he can win.
我和他之间经常会有分歧
We often don't see eye to eye, he and I.
但我们还是可以共事的
And yet, there are ways we can work together.
好吧  委员会那里可能是我错了
Okay, maybe I made a mistake with the committee.
我有时候会有些自以为是
I can be self-righteous.
我是想清理党派  我们的党派
I'm trying to clean up the party. Our party.
结果我说错话了
And I end up speaking out of turn.
少来"不怪你是我的错"这一套了
It's enough with the, "It's me, not you."
你到底能做什么  艾力克斯
What can you deliver, Alex?
我可以不碍事
I can get out of the way.
这话太含糊  而且不够
Well, that sounds vague and inadequate.
我想知道泰瑞·乌麦克和黑人党团是怎么回事
I want to know what's up with Terry Womack and the Black Caucus.
总统和乌麦克议员
The president and Congressman Womack,
他们关系很好
they have a good relationship.
当然了  但我可不想看到泰瑞让你们失望
I'm sure they do. But I would hate to see Terry let you down.
如果失去了乌麦克和黑人党团  我们周一就完了
If we lose Womack and the Black Caucus, we're done on Monday.
有几个新人我可以搭上关系
There are a few freshmen I could reach out to.
他们或许能让黑人党团同心
They might help keep the CBC together.
你想当少数党党鞭
You wanna be minority whip.
如果我够格
Only if I deserve to be.
我准备回去了
I'm trying to get back.
刘易斯议员又迟到了二十分钟
Congressman Lewis is 20 minutes late as usual.
发信人: 旧友/新敌
我警告过你  叫走那些狗  否则还会继续
能让他进金融服务委员会吗
Is there a spot for him on financial services?
警察内部备忘录早已断定商店爆炸系因燃气泄漏后
联调局才被召来  新证据显示"袭击"系捏造
道格  待着别动
Doug, stay where you are.
你不是说你让中情局别插手了吗
I thought you said you were telling the CIA to stand down.
是啊
I did.
你保证过麦卡伦会老实的
So, contrary to your assurances that Macallan would behave,
现在却出现消息泄露
we're now dealing with a leak.
-他不想惹麻烦  -你怎么知道他想要什么
- He doesn't want trouble. - How do you know what he wants?
你去找到他  带过来
You find him and you get him here.
只要他知道我们让步了
As soon as he knows we've backed off,
他就会消失的  我保证
he will disappear. I promise.
不  你的保证对我毫无意义
No, that word means nothing to me.
警察内部备忘录早已断定商店爆炸系因燃气泄漏后
联调局才被召来  新证据显示"袭击"系捏造
你写好声明了吗
You have a statement?
还会不会有其他重大的
You anticipate any other big WikiLeaks info dumps
维基解密事件
coming down the pike?
-你会知道的  -等我需要知道的时候
- You'll know-- - When I need to know.
我知道
I know.
也就是上了CNN的时候吧
Which is apparently whenever it hits CNN.
联调局之前高度戒备  他们调查每个威胁
FBI was on high alert. They investigated every threat.
冷静
Calm down.
我很冷静  道格  民众不冷静
I am calm, Doug. The public's not calm.
每次失足都被强调  放大
Every misstep is highlighted and heightened.
他们想知道选举到底怎么回事
They wanna know what happened with their election.
我们正在解决
We're fixing it.
他们怕的就是这个
That's what they're afraid of.
声明是关于联调局的  大家都信任联调局
The statement's about the FBI. Everybody trusts the FBI.
丽萨·威廉姆斯是谁
Hey, who's Lisa Williams?
我不知道  怎么了
I don't know. Why?
《先驱报》有人打电话来
Somebody from the Herald called.
问你认不认识她
They were just wondering if you knew her.
不认识
I don't.
我需要五分钟审阅
I need five minutes with this.
-给你关门吗  -关
- Open or closed? - Closed.
我那份声明怎么样
Am I good with that statement?
我做好标记了  在我桌子上
I marked it up. It's on my desk.
安东尼·莫雷蒂  2次通话
把选举交回给各州
Throwing the election back to the states,
让我们的把握变小了
it gives us less certainty.
我觉得周一之前我们没法办妥
I don't think we can get it done by Monday.
我们都已经忙了几周了  弗兰西斯
We've been working at it for weeks, Francis.
克莱尔  别因为当职而变得小心翼翼
Claire, don't let the office make you careful.
国会从来没让我失望过
The halls of Congress have never failed me.
是  但那些职业政客
Yes, but the career politicians,
他们从没这么步调一致过
they are more entrenched than ever.
现在有了新众议院  里面的人你不认识
There's a new House, with members you don't know.
我们得把重点
We need to move the playing field
放回到人民的期望上
back to the imaginations of the people.
你这么相信田纳西和俄亥俄的选民吗
You have that much faith in the voters in Tennessee and Ohio?
他们会选你的  我确定
They're going to choose you. I just know it.
好吧
All right.
安排会议  我会听他们说的  你赢了
Set up a meeting. I'll hear them all out. You win.
是我们  是我们赢了
Both of us. Both of us.
晚上好
Good evening.
艾瑞克
Eric.
就像是在外面吧
Feel like you're outside?
你不是应该限制在三十分钟之内吗
Aren't you supposed to limit it to 30 minutes?
-天啊  可别  -把健身调整好就不必
- Oh, God, Jesus, no. - Not if you calibrate the workout.
我没事
Oh, I'm feeling fine.
你要听从你的身体
It's all about listening to your body.
它会告诉你什么时候该休息
It'll tell you when it's time to rest.
你有时也该听医生的  弗兰西斯
You should listen to the doctors some of the time, Francis.
我确定安德伍德夫妇很担心
I know the Underwoods were worried.
因为他们愿意做交易
Because they were ready to deal.
跟我做交易
To deal with me.
-你能肯定吗  -非常肯定
- You're sure it's for real? - Sure as I can be.
好  再联系
Okay, we'll be in touch.
好
Okay.
给他打回去
So call him back.
成功让几个民主党人改主意了
Making progress on a couple of Dems.
阿尔斯波议员也要回心转意了
Think Congressman Alspaugh is about to turn.
我们周日见他
We'll see him on Sunday.
为什么要等
Why wait?
我们明天得和国会黑人党团见面
We need to meet with the Congressional Black Caucus. Tomorrow.
他们是安德伍德的
They're in Underwood's pocket.
是啊  能让我们说句话吗  各位
Yeah. Can you give us a second, everybody?
好的
Uh, sure.
走吧
Come on.
谢谢
Thank you.
我刚得到内部消息
I just got word from somebody inside.
乌麦克在失去对党团的控制
Womack is losing control of the caucus.
要是你能拿下他们  周一就赢了
If you win them, you win Monday.
我们应该试试
We should try.
好吧  我们试试吧
All right, fine. Let's do it.
-我去安排  -今晚结束了吗
- I'll set it up. - Are we done here tonight?
你还得打几个电话
You still have a few calls.
马克  我在想我们是不是能
Mark, I was thinking, maybe we could, um...
取消明晚在费城的活动
cancel tomorrow night in Philadelphia.
一趟出行和活动都不能取消  不应该取消
We can't cancel any trip, or any event. We shouldn't.
让我们稍稍歇歇会大有好处的
A second to catch our breath would be really helpful, I think.
就得这样  汉娜  需要的话你就休息一下吧
This is what it is, Hannah. If you need to take a break, you can.
亲爱的  我们一整周都没睡了
Darling, we haven't slept all week.
你累坏了
You're exhausted.
-我  只是说说  -下一个打给谁
- I... Just an idea. - What's my next call?
但你不快乐
But you're not enjoying yourself.
因为他不肯听我的
Because he won't listen to me.
众议院他赢不了
He can't win in the House.
我说的不是他  我说的是你
I'm not talking about him. I'm talking about you.
我快不快乐又有什么区别呢
What difference does it make whether I'm enjoying myself or not?
这不才是最重要的吗
Isn't that what this is all about?
你就不能...先体验它一下吗
Can't you just... live in it for a second?
你现在掌权了
You are in charge.
-对  但是  -过来
- Yes, but-- - Come here.
过来
Come.
等你明早醒来
You could wake up tomorrow...
你可以
and...
比如  喂孩子们吃饭
I don't know, feed the children...
挑起战争
start a war...
你知道吗  我很抱歉
You know what? I'm sorry.
我不应该把我想的都说出来
I shouldn't think out loud, that's all.
不  你说得对
No, you're right.
我们别谈这房间外发生的事了
Let's not talk about anything that happens outside of this room.
制裁的目标是俄罗斯的寡头阶层
The sanctions are meant to target the oligarch class in Russia.
我和佩特罗夫总统谈判之前
And the more members we have on board
我们能争取到越多成员的支持
before I sit down with President Petrov,
这问题就能越快得到解决
the quicker this will resolve itself.
已经在做了  我们准备出售一些战略储备
We are. We are prepared to release some of our strategic reserves
以平稳油价
to keep prices down.
联系卡斯皮大使  再给我争取15分钟
Contact Ambassador Caspi and buy me 15 more minutes.
别把这当成是和安德伍德夫妇的交易
Uh, please don't think of this as a deal with the Underwoods.
说实在的  他们可能周一就走了
To be frank, they could be gone by Monday.
但当然了  我不希望这样
That's not what I wish, of course.
但要知道  在这件事上
But know that you are
你更多是跟我合作  而不是跟他们
working more with me on this than with them.
沃茨议员
Congressman Watts.
州长  真高兴你今天来见我们
Governor, we're so happy you could join us today.
我也很高兴  黑人群体应该得到更好的政策
As am I. The black community deserves so much better
而不是弗兰克·安德伍德失败的政策
than Frank Underwood's failed policies.
这我们都同意
That we can agree on.
我期待你的政纲
I look forward to hearing about your platform.
-我们开始吗  -不  抱歉
- Shall we? - Oh, no, I'm sorry.
我们还得再处理一些闭门的
We have just a bit more private caucus business
党团议程
to attend to first.
你说什么
Excuse me?
这是国会黑人党团的会议
This is a meeting of the Congressional Black Caucus.
我知道  所以我们才来
Well, I understand. That's... why we're here.
跟我说的是九点  现在已经过了一个小时了
I was told 9:00, and it's already been an hour.
应该叫你十点来的
You should have been told 10:00.
你会有机会跟我们谈的
And you will get your opportunity to address us.
很感谢你的耐心等待
I appreciate your patience.
我不会低声下气的
I'm not gonna beg.
对  你要微笑
No, you're gonna smile.
在田纳西被捕的穆罕默德·卡拉比
The Muhammed Kalabi they arrested in Tennessee
和哈里发国并无关联
is not the Kalabi connected to ICO.
你能证明这不是单纯的搞错了吗
Can you prove it wasn't just a bureaucratic mix-up?
目前还没有证据
Uh, not yet.
还有什么
What else?
最后一宗压制投票诉讼
Uh, final voter suppression lawsuit
被踢回了下级法院
was kicked back to the lower court,
高院的僵持助长了混乱局面
SCOTUS deadlock is feeding the chaos.
你看报吗  肖恩
Do you read the paper, Sean?
比利三天前就署名发表了关于这个的报道
Billy got a byline on that three days ago.
宣战怎么样
Declaration of war?
安德伍德之前还决心满满
Underwood was so evangelical,
但他已经几周没提起这个了
but hasn't mentioned it in weeks.
行了  够了  够了
All right, that's enough. That's enough.
丽萨·威廉姆斯
Lisa Williams.
丽莎·威廉姆斯怎么了
What about Lisa Williams?
我看见你和她交谈了
I saw you talking.
我认为她这条线可能值得追查
I thought she might be a lead worth pursuing.
并不
She's not.
她只是在利用在报上看到的东西
She's using what she read in the paper
博取关注或是发点小财
to get attention or a little cash.
我调查了一下
I did some digging.
她和瑞秋·波斯纳
She and Rachel Posner
都去过一个叫团契的教堂
both went to a church called the Fellowship.
-瑞秋失踪了  -打住
- Rachel disappeared-- - Stop.
别再扯这些关于死去姑娘的阴谋论了
No more conspiracy theories about dead girls.
但人们喜欢看死去姑娘的故事
But people love stories about dead girls.
下一场众议院投票就在后天了
The next House vote is the day after tomorrow.
国民坐立不安  义愤填膺
The natives are restless, outraged,
而且说实话  害怕了
just plain scared, actually.
他们希望美国不会一夜天翻地覆
They want to wake up in the America that they fell asleep in.
卡拉比那条线再挖挖
Dig deeper on the Kalabi lead.
看看能不能和安德伍德联系到一起去
See if you can connect Underwood to it.
这是詹姆斯·S·布雷迪媒体接待室
So, this is the James S. Brady press briefing room.
我们脚下其实是个游泳池
And under our feet is actually a swimming pool.
是由畸形儿基金会为
It was built by the March of Dimes
富兰克林·罗斯福总统建造的
for President Franklin Roosevelt,
他患了小儿麻痹症
who had polio.
泳池是他唯一的健身场所
And this pool was really the only way for him to exercise.
罗斯福总统大部分时间
It was, an open secret
都是在轮椅上度过  这已是个公开的秘密了
that the president used a wheelchair most of the time.
因此白宫
Which is why the White House
是首批有残疾人专用通道的政府建筑之一
was one of the first wheelchair-accessible government buildings.
-但大家都装作他能走路吗  -是的
- But everyone pretended he could walk? - Yes.
-这很有风度  -是的
- That's a bit of grace. - Yeah.
大家都心照不宣
A thing not spoken?
是的  这座大楼因为他的残疾而进行了改建
Yeah, this building literally changed because of his disability.
但人们都很尊敬他
But people just respected him,
尊敬他的...
respected his, uh--
嗯
Right.
总统办公室曾承载了很重的分量
That office used to carry so much weight,
和很多尊敬
so much, respect.
你觉得现在已经不是如此了吗
You don't think it does anymore?
不不  我没那个意思
No, oh, no, no! I'm not saying that.
我是在故意为难你  我明白你的意思
I was giving you a hard time. I know what you meant.
抱歉  我无意打扰你们参观的
Anyway, sorry, didn't mean to hijack the tour.
继续...
Moving on...
先生们  我们可以见你们了
Gentlemen, we're ready for you now.
我今天可以在这儿
I could come here today
谈论大麻和可卡因的
and talk about federal sentencing disparities
联邦量刑差异
between crack and cocaine,
这其中显然存在种族因素
which obviously are racially motivated.
打断一下  你是断定滥用大麻的问题
I'm sorry, but are you asserting that the crack epidemic
只在黑人群体中存在吗
is exclusive to the black community?
不  完全不是
No, not at all.
但我觉得可以说  量刑差异
But I think it's fair to say that sentencing discrepancies
对少数群体的影响尤为严重
have disproportionately affected minority populations.
我们不只关注一个问题
We're not one-issue voters.
当然不是  这正是我的意思
Of course not. That's what I'm getting at.
今天会议的主旨就是扩展我们的纲领
The whole point of today's meeting is to broaden our platform.
共和党总是拿犯罪说事  州长
Republicans are always dwelling on crime, Governor.
我就是来沟通的
Well, I'm here to have a dialogue.
我们希望你能拿出一个方案来
We expected you to come in here with a plan.
我确实准备了一套方案
And I do have a plan.
专注于个别繁琐的立法不叫方案
Concentrating on a few pieces of onerous legislation is not a plan.
让我们把话说清楚...
Let's be clear...
这样的说辞我们听过
That kind of talk we've heard before.
-我是共和党人  -又来了
- I'm a Republican. - Here we go.
你们没有好好听我说
You're not listening.
我想帮助你们自力更生
Look, I want to help you help yourselves.
不可理喻
Unbelievable.
这就是我的纲领
That's my platform.
是吗  我听够了
Well... I've heard enough.
还有谁有问题想问州长
So, does anyone else have any questions for the governor?
我倒是有个问题
Well, I have a question.
弗兰西斯·安德伍德到底给了你们什么好处
What has Francis Underwood ever done for you?
今天早上的这出戏
This little charade this morning...
-演得好  真精彩  -威尔
- Well done. Quite an act. - Will.
-州长  -我说真的
- Governor. - No, but really.
你们也许和我有分歧
See, you may have differences with me...
你们也许真心不赞同我的观点
You may have genuine differences with me.
但最关键的就是这一点  "真心"
But see, that's the operative word, "genuine."
能否麻烦你们哪位给我解释一下
Can someone here please explain to me
你们为什么还对
why you all are still so loyal
弗兰西斯·安德伍德和民主党这么忠诚
to Francis Underwood and the Democrats?
总有一天
One of these days
在座的各位会意识到
the members of this room will realize
目前的现状  你们要负多大的责任
how much you actually prop up the status quo.
你们捞着什么好处了吗
And how's that working for ya?
威尔  我们先感谢各位先生女士见我们吧
Will, why don't we thank the gentlemen and women for their time?
你们犯了个错误
You've made a mistake.
我们提议在两个未能在安全港日之前
What we're proposing is a new election in the two states
选举人到华盛顿进行最后投票前6天
选出有效选举人的州
that weren't able to provide valid electors
重新举行大选
by the safe harbor date.
还能这么做
Can we even do this?
安静  大家安静
Hold on. Hold on, everyone!
我想知道
I'd like to know,
司法部长是什么立场
where does the attorney general stand on this?
正在研究  不过也同意了
Looking into it, but on board.
鲍勃  这种事根本没有先例
Bob, there's no precedent here.
没有现成的规则
There's no playbook.
我们只能在宪法里寻找启示
We can look to the Constitution for inspiration,
但它不是操作指南
but not for instruction.
周四的投票表明民主党人渐渐想明白了
Thursday's vote showed Democrats are coming to their senses.
我们输了一场投票  乔丹
We lost one vote, Jordan.
这事完全可能搞成拉锯战
We can go back and forth like this forever.
作为在场少数的几个共和党  我必须要说
As one of the few Republicans in the room, it needs to be said.
我们国家的稳定
The stability of our country
要比总统职位重要得多
is more important than the presidency.
除非民众认为他们的总统
Not if people believe the president
是秘密会议指定的
is being chosen behind closed doors.
这是宪法里写明的程序
A process that is laid out in the Constitution.
而这个程序完全可能让我们
The same process that can keep us gridlocked
再僵持两年
for the next two years.
决定权应该且必须归于众议院
The House should and will decide.
特拉华州只有一个众议员
Delaware has one congressman.
如果两年后你的对手告诉选民  是你
How will that play in Austin when your opponent in two years
让特拉华这样的小州和德州有相同的影响力
tells voters that you allowed a state like Delaware
你在奥斯丁还要怎么待
to have the same influence as Texas?
你们许多在任议员都将可能败选
A lot of you incumbents will be in danger of losing your seats.
就是这样
And there it is.
看啊  看看他们
Look. Look at them.
这就是忌惮失败的表情
That is the look of contemplating loss.
失败
Loss...
是这里所有人唯一听从的选民
the only constituent that anyone in this room really listens to.
我个人想听一下
I, for one, would like to hear
总统对此的看法
how the president feels about all this.
-我已经...  -我想我们可以
- Well, I've made my... - I think we could...
我是问总统先生  您刚才一直没说什么
No, Mr. President. You haven't spoken much here.
我们相信一人一票
We believe in one person, one vote.
如果不能做到这点  我们国家还算什么
If we take that away, then what is this country?
对不对  总统先生
Isn't that right, Mr. President?
完全正确  总统女士
Absolutely, Madam President.
等等  等下  我往下挪挪
Wait, hold it. Let me just move down a bit.
我老是要从讲台上滑下来
I keep slipping off the podium.
-你接着我  -好些了吗
- You got me. - That better?
嗯  好爽
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
话说林肯室
So the Lincoln...
那真是他的办公室吗
That was actually his office?
能不说工作吗
Can we... can we not?
-你能  把我往上托一托吗  -好
- Can you... can you move me up a bit? - Yeah.
好了
Okay.
-还顺利吗  -再看吧
- How'd it go? - We'll see.
我需要你再过一遍南极洲事件的声明稿
I need you to look over the Antarctica statement again.
都听你的
Whatever you need.
陪我走走吧
Walk with me?
我有点担心弗兰西斯
I'm worried about Francis.
-为什么  -我可能需要你帮我一把
- Why? - I might need you to save me.
-这样是不行的  -为什么
- This is not going to work. - Why?
如果他没赢  那我还是输
If he loses, I still lose.
他不能站在圈外看着我们忙活
He cannot be on the outside looking in.
他会赢的
He'll win.
你真的这么想
You actually believe that?
当然  为什么不呢
Sure... why not?
这本就是赌一把
It was a wager.
有潜在收益  所以有必要赌
The potential gains made it necessary.
完全是浪费我的时间
It was a complete waste of my time.
如果你还不开始扭转局势
If you don't start turning things around,
你他妈就得滚蛋  明白吗
you're going to be out on your fucking ass. You understand?
明白
I do.
我该跟你说明白一件事  州长
I should explain something to you, Governor.
如果你再那样跟我说话
If you ever talk to me like that again...
我会确保你这辈子再赢不了一场选举
I'll make sure you never win another election in your life.
-你在威胁我吗  -不  我只是把话说开
- Are you threatening me? - No, I'm enlightening you.
安东尼·莫雷蒂
纪念基金
康威州长  你好  先生
Governor Conway. Hello, sir.
情况如何  我来看看
How you doin'? Take a peek,
-你不介意吧  机长  -州长
- if you don't mind, Captain? - Governor.
我过去也开过飞机
I used to fly, too, you know.
引擎的最大推力是多少
What kinda max thrust you get on these engines?
-约六千四百磅  -六千四百磅
- About 6,400 pounds. - 6,400 pounds.
我过去开的飞机更大  推力更强
I used to fly something a lot bigger, a lot more power,
但飞机上的武器很重
but it was so weighed down with all the weaponry,
像在驾驶坦克
it was like flying a tank.
不如你让我开会儿
Why don't you let me in for a second,
让我控制操纵杆
just flip me the controls?
抱歉  先生  不行
I'm sorry, sir. I can't.
别这样  我...
Come on, I...
我只是想感受一下操纵杆的力道
I just want to feel the weight on the stick for a second.
我也想  但你不在飞行计划中
I wish I could, but, uh, you're not on the flight plan.
你知道我经验丰富吧
You know I've been in situations,
我遭遇过攻击
where, like, I've been shot at.
你明白吧
You realize that, right?
你觉得我驾驭不了十千米高空中的双引擎
You don't think I can handle a twin engine at 35,000 feet,
飞机还是平稳地飞越农田
straight and level over some farm country?
拜托  先生
I mean, come on, sir.
先生
Sir.
您还是回主舱吧
You should probably go back to the main cabin.
你知道我会成为总统吧
You know I'm gonna be the president, right?
-希望如此  先生  -你希望如此
- I hope so, sir. - You hope so?
我只是说我支持你  先生
I just mean I'm pulling for you, sir.
我一定会成为总统
I'm gonna be the president,
你也一定要把那该死的操纵杆给我
and you're going to flip me those motherfucking controls.
威尔  过来
Will, come on.
-干吗  你想怎样  -我只是
- What? What do you want? - I just
得跟你谈一会儿  行吗
I need to talk to you for a minute, please.
我只是在跟飞行员聊天
I was just talking to the pilots.
行  你得冷静下来  行吗
Okay, I need you to calm down, okay?
呼吸
Breathe.
威尔  不如你坐下
Will, why don't you sit down?
不如你他妈闭嘴
Why don't you shut the fuck up?
我要炒了你
I'll fire you.
把你留在跑道上
I'll leave you on the goddamn tarmac.
好吧
Okay.
你他妈想怎样
What the fuck are you gonna do?
坐下来  别耍孩子气
Sit down and try and act like an adult...
至少要有点下任美国总统的样子
or at least like the next President of the United States.
坐下
Sit.
雅加达星报
他们是谁
Who are they?
或许是印尼的秘密警察
Maybe Indonesian secret police?
不付钱会怎样
What if we don't pay?
还有其他买家吗
Are there other buyers?
不清楚
I don't know.
我会处理好的
I'll take care of it.
-怎么做  -别问我
- How? - Don't ask how.
我会找回麦卡伦
I'll get Macallan back.
显然这事得保密
Obviously, this stays between us.
说"谢谢  道格"
Say, "Thank you, Doug."
谢谢  道格
Thank you, Doug.
我们在公交车上认识的
We met on a bus.
她当时在听歌
She was listening to music.
我问她要不要去我以前常去的一间教堂
And I asked her to go to this church I used to go to.
-那是在哪  -马里兰
- Where was that? - Maryland.
冬离团契
The Winter's Run Fellowship.
巴尔的摩往北一小时路程
About an hour north of Baltimore.
然后呢
So, then what?
我们就是...
I don't know. We just...
成了朋友  然后就超越了朋友
became friends. And then it became more than that.
开始每晚在一起
Started spending every night together.
后来  她告诉我有个男人
At some point, she told me about this guy
常常过去查看她的情况
who used to come around to check on her.
-那男人长什么样  -我没见过他
- What'd he look like? - I never saw him.
只是有时  她说他要来
Just sometimes she said he was coming,
就没法跟我在一起
so she couldn't hang out.
她并不怎么跟我讲他的事
She wouldn't really tell me anything about him.
你没事吧
Everything okay?
没事  失陪一下
Yeah, do you mind?
我朋友在那边  我得去见他
I just need to see my friend up there.
你好吗
How are you doing?
谢谢
Thanks.
你认为那儿有石油
You think there's oil there.
你想争取开采权
You're positioning to stake a claim.
南极洲并没有俄国军队
There are no Russian troops in Antarctica.
我们愿对《南极条约》缔约国
We're willing to recommend changes
提出修改建议
to the Antarctic Treaty parties.
安德伍德夫妇被赶出白宫后  你会怎么样
What happens to you when the Underwoods are ejected from office?
到大学去教国际关系
You teach international relations at a university?
还是加入智囊团
Or work for a think tank?
我还没想那么远
I haven't thought that far ahead.
你应该有吧
I think you have.
你不觉得全世界迟早会发现
How long do you expect the world to believe
那是你的军队吗
those aren't your soldiers?
你喜欢替安德伍德夫妇工作吗
Do you like working for the Underwoods?
你有多忠诚
How loyal are you?
关键时刻  你会支持他们
When the time comes, will you stand with them...
还是抛弃他们
or not?
我明天离开
I leave tomorrow.
关于制裁的新闻会在周一爆出
News of the sanctions will hit Monday.
你走之前我们见个面
Let's meet before you go.
你是外交专家  专业人士
You're a career diplomat, a professional.
或许因此我信任你
Maybe that's why I trust you.
你会照顾他们
Then you take care of them,
他们感觉好了  就会照顾你
so they feel good and they take care of you.
那你就会感觉好...
So you feel good because...
瑞秋美丽动人
I mean, Rachel was really beautiful.
你站在街对面就能看得出来
You could tell that from across the street.
但我从来没有隔着街看过她
I never saw her from across the street, though.
仔细想想是不是很奇妙
Isn't that a funny thing to think about?
我觉得  有时候
A lot of people, I think,
很多人隔着街就能认出他们的心上人
they spot the one they love from across the street sometimes.
比如说他们出门办事
It's like they're running an errand,
碰巧看见他们的心上人
and they happen to spot the one they love
在街对面  办着别的事
across the street running a different errand.
心里一阵激动
There's this sudden thrill, like...
因为你的爱人
while the person you love
和你居住在同一个世界
is inhabiting the same world as you.
而他们只是很随意地
And they're just walking around,
出门买个维生素水之类的
buying, I don't know... Vitaminwater,
或许他们这么做时  知道你爱着他们
and maybe they know that you love them while they're doing it,
或许他们因此会对店员友善
and maybe it means they're nice to a cashier.
但是我从来没有隔着街看过她
I never got to see her from across the street, though.
从来没有
It just never happened.
别烫伤自己了
I don't want you to burn yourself.
不会烫伤的
No burning, no.
瑞秋爱抽烟
Rachel liked to smoke.
她说打算戒掉
She said she was gonna stop,
但她定了个规则  只有我们一起听
but she would have a rule that she'd only smoke
我们共同喜爱的乐队时  她才能抽烟
when we listened to this one band we both loved.
因为那是仪式
Because of the ceremony.
"这该成为一个仪式"  她这么说的
"It should be a ceremony," it's what she said.
即使是口香糖
Well, even if it's gum,
我还是想到外面嚼
I still prefer to step outside to chew it.
像是在点燃一根美味的香烟
Like lighting a delicious cigarette.
我们所怀念的  那种仪式感
The things we miss, the rituals...
我先走了
Excuse me.
-她不喜欢我  -她以后会的
- She doesn't like me. - She will.
感谢你过来和他见面
Thanks for coming out here and meeting with him.
你知道法律上  你无法赶走克莱尔·安德伍德
You know you can't legally remove Claire Underwood,
即便你在众议院获胜
even if you win in the House?
我正在想办法
I'm working on that.
我没兴趣
I'm not interested.
他需要你  我需要你
He needs you. I need you.
国家也需要你
So does the country.
我不是政客
I'm not a politician.
我能下达命令  也能遵从命令
I can give orders, I can follow orders
我知道何时该闭嘴
and I know when the hell to shut up.
你是个稳重的人  国家需要这种人
And you're a steady hand, which, again, the country needs.
-我可不当康威的替死鬼  -你不会的
- I'm not gonna be Conway's patsy. - No, you're not.
他是个难相处的人
He's a difficult man to be around.
已经结束了
It's over. It's over.
宪法程序选择了克莱尔·安德伍德
The process chose Claire Underwood.
我们会有办法的
We'll get there.
你会被称为副总统
You'll be called vice president,
但实际上  你将做到更多
but you will be, de facto, something more.
你去那儿做什么
What were you doing there?
我去问赛斯·格雷森关于丽萨·威廉姆斯的事
I asked Seth Grayson about Lisa Williams.
你为什么会认为可以这么做
Why the hell did you think that was an appropriate thing to do?
我不是叫你别管这条线索了吗
Didn't I tell you to drop this lead?
这还算线索吗  因为没人在查
Is it still a lead? Because nobody's on it.
没人在查是因为她是瘾君子
Nobody's on it because she's a junkie,
而她告诉我的一切
and everything she said to me
卢卡斯·古德温的宣言里都有
is in the Lucas Goodwin manifesto,
而宣言的每一字每一句  都被网上各大论坛
which has been picked apart by every message board
和阴谋论者掰烂嚼碎了
and conspiracy theorist on the Internet.
一开始  格雷森说对她的名字没印象
At first, Grayson said her name didn't ring a bell,
然后他突然联系我
but then he called me out of the blue
问我是不是还在查这个事
and asked me if we were still looking into it.
所以我就查了
So I followed up.
你偷看了我的笔记
You looked through my notes.
滚
You're out.
-什么  -你被开除了  杰弗瑞斯
- What? - You're fired, Jeffries.
这是个故事  我在跟进这个故事
It's a story. I was following it.
我不希望你跟着我干了
I don't want you on my team.
滚出我的办公室
Get out of my office.
我们知道我们能赢下这两个州
We know we can win both states.
为什么不接受这个交易
Why would we not take this deal?
不  安德伍德夫妇想重新投票
No. The Underwoods want a revote
是因为他们知道拿不下众议院  而我们能
because they know they can't win in the House. We can.
我们要做个交易  逼克莱尔·安德伍德辞职
We need to make a deal that forces Claire Underwood to resign.
-她有那么重要吗  -我能说两句吗
- And why does that matter? - If I may?
-议长女士  -就国会而言
- Madam Speaker. - Speaking from the Hill,
作为副总统
as vice president,
她可以利用这个平台公开抹黑你的所有动作
she'll have a public pulpit to discredit your every move.
美国副总统官邸
我会把克莱尔·安德伍德流放到海军天文台I'm going to exile Claire Underwood to the Naval Observatory
让她整天在东南亚出席国葬仪式
and stack her schedule with state funerals in Southeast Asia.
她别想参与白宫的决策
She'll never see the inside of the West Wing,
更别提干涉总统了
let alone the Oval.
你需要布洛哈特在你身边支持你
You need Brockhart by your side, supporting you.
我不想再听布洛哈特的事了
I don't want to hear about Brockhart.
重要的是让威尔当上总统
What matters is that Will becomes president.
安德伍德在你的政府里会造成巨大破坏的
Underwood in office can cause an enormous amount damage.
反过来如果他们输了  他们就全完了
Whereas, if they lose, they're losers.
我希望这场选举是在我
I want this election to be between me
和弗兰西斯·安德伍德之间
and Francis Underwood.
这你说了不算
Well, it isn't up to you.
麦卡锡议长不会让这个议案进入投票的
Speaker McCarthy isn't letting this particular bill to the floor,
除非我们附加一项修正案
unless we have an amendment attached
将克莱尔·安德伍德赶走
that removes Claire Underwood.
威尔
Will...
如果你希望白宫里有位愿意合作的总统
Now, if you expect a willing partner in the White House,
那你最好让议案原样进入表决
you'd better let that bill get to the floor as is.
如果你坐进总统办公室  威尔
If you get to the Oval, Will,
那时是你更需要议长  而不是反过来
you're gonna need the Speaker more than she needs you.
我这就给她打回去
So, I'm gonna call her back,
然后你要道歉
and you are going to apologize.
威尔
Will.
威尔  回来
Will, get back here!
威尔
Will!
别逼他了
Enough.
关门
Shut the door.
你看着像死人
You look like death.
我联系不上绑匪了
I can't get in touch with the kidnappers.
快一天了  什么消息都没有
It's been radio silence for almost 24 hours.
有传言说他已经不在绑匪手上了
There's rumors they don't even have him anymore.
这事我不能再瞒着总统了
I can't keep this from the president any longer.
好吧
Okay.
那我会告诉他你帮了好大的忙
And then I'll tell him what a big help you've been.
再过几小时制裁就要生效了
Sanctions hit in a couple of hours.
你要么和杜兰特国务卿谈
Deal with Secretary Durant
要么对付几个愤怒的亿万富翁去吧
or with some very unhappy billionaires.
你要让我在南极洲任意开采石油
You will allow me to exploit whatever oil I find in Antarctica.
我告诉你为什么
And I'll tell you why.
我手上有料
I have something.
或者说有你们想要的人
Or rather, someone you need.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你们政府里有人
Someone in your administration
愿花大钱换他平安回国
was willing to pay a great deal of money for his safe return.
你的艾丹·麦卡伦
Your Aidan Macallan.
他在这里  就在克里姆林宫里
He's here. In the Kremlin.
不然你以为是谁泄的密
Who do you think orchestrated that leak?
看来他知道的不少啊
Seems to know quite a lot.
失陪一下  你们国务卿来了
Excuse me one moment. The Secretary of State is here.
-国务卿女士  -先生们
- Madam Secretary. - Gentlemen.
想必你认识艾丹吧
You must know Aidan?
我想我不认识他
I don't believe I do.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
-你是美国人  -是
- You're American? - I am.
开始会谈之前  我想让你知道
Before we begin, I'd just like you to know that
你们的总统和前总统都在线上
the president and the former president are on the line.
凯茜
Cathy...
你愿意的话可以接听
You can pick up the phone, if you like.
总统先生
Mr. President.
你最好先回华盛顿
It's best you come back to Washington.
有什么发现吗
Find anything yet?
还没
Not yet.
再次感谢  巴恩斯先生
Thank you again, Mr. Barnes,
谢谢你让我看
for letting me take a look.
我不会看太久
I won't be long.
这就是全部吗
This is everything?
这是他们从佐伊的公寓寄来的一切
This is everything they sent from Zoe's apartment.
我就是
I just, you know...
我不忍扔掉任何东西
I just can't seem to throw anything out.
只是些文件  但是
I mean, it's just papers, but...
不管怎样  你自便
Anyway, I'll leave you to it.
-好  谢谢  -没事
- Okay. Thank you. - Yeah.
道格·斯坦普  瑞秋·波斯纳
好吧
Okay.
黑人党团  不是吧
The Black Caucus? Really?
我喜欢马克  因为我总是知道他的立场
I like Mark, because I always know where he stands.
通常是对人步步紧逼
It's usually on someone's neck.
你给自己争取到了什么  一天时间吗
What did you buy yourselves, another day?
足够跟大卫·拉斯姆森谈了
Enough time to talk to David Rasmussen,
显然你早就跟他谈过
who you clearly spoke to before.
然后又见了乔丹·萨多斯基
And to meet with Jordan Sadowsky
和剩下的共和党领导人
and the rest of the Republican leadership.
那星期二呢  星期三呢
And what happens Tuesday? Or Wednesday?
我能让大卫和众议院
Look, I... I can have David and the House
每次会议都对此进行投票
vote on this every single session.
我们背景不同
Our backgrounds are different,
但内心里我们都是穷小子
but we're both hardscrabble boys at heart.
我们需要最后一个字  最后一击
We need the last word, last blow,
最后一举
last move.
我们能让众议院通过议案
We can push the bill through the House
在田纳西州和俄亥俄州重新选举总统
for a new election for president in Tennessee and Ohio.
麦卡锡议长不会允许那种事发生
Speaker McCarthy won't let that happen.
但我能说服她
But I could... convince her
如果你辞职
if you were to step down,
我们在田纳西州和俄亥俄州
and our full tickets president and vice president
同时进行总统和副总统的选举
run against each other in Tennessee and Ohio.
那可不行  那可不行
Well, to hell with that. Well, to hell with that.
我们接受交易  我想这是正确的做法
We'll make the deal. I think this is the right thing to do.
明天我会宣布
Tomorrow, I'll announce my intention
在重新投票后我就辞职
to step down after the revote.
我会通知议长让议案进入投票表决
I'll let the Speaker know to put the bill on the floor.
我们还有一件非常重要的事
We have one more outstanding piece of business,
最高法院提名人
the Supreme Court nominee.
我们需要任命个人来打破四四僵局
We'll need to appoint someone to break the four-four deadlock.
批准国会的新选举日
Approve Congress' new election date.
我们有几个人选
We, uh, have several people in mind.
我希望你们任命伊丽莎白·本森
I want you to appoint Elizabeth Benson.
她足够开放  你可以接受
Well, she's liberal enough for you to swallow,
必要的时候又足够保守
and conservative enough when it counts.
但我们没时间开参议院听证会
Yes, but we don't have time for Senate hearings.
我可以让参议院休会
I can make a recess happen.
竞选活动上见
I'll see you on the campaign trail.
那置我于何地  艾力克斯
Where does that leave me, huh, Alex?
我冒了巨大风险
I went out on a limb here.
如果我们没拿下众议院  那怎么办
If we don't have a vote in the House, then what?
马克·厄舍是你的朋友  不是我的
Mark Usher is your friend, not mine.
马克·厄舍不是任何人的朋友
Mark Usher's no one's friend.
弗兰西斯·安德伍德什么也没赢  好吗
Francis Underwood hasn't won a thing, okay?
威尔·康威有可能  很大的可能
And there's a good... More than a good chance that Will Conway
会成为下一任美国总统
will be the next President of the United States.
能让我单独待会儿吗  这几天太艰难了
Could you give me a moment? It's been a difficult few days.
好点吗
Better?
嗯
Yes.
我们不能按原计划让众议院周一投票
We couldn't let the House vote proceed on Monday.
为什么
Why not?
因为你会输的
Because you would've lost.
即使康威当了总统
Even if Conway took the presidency,
有你  我们还是会有立足之地
we would've had a foothold with you.
我们可以破坏他们  就像对沃克夫妇那样
We could've sabotaged, just like we did with the Walkers.
康威夫妇不是沃克夫妇
The Conways are not the Walkers.
那不是你能决定的
It wasn't your decision to make.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你自己说的  你只是代总统
You said it yourself. You're only acting.
我赞同厄舍
I agreed with Usher
是因为他会不惜一切
because he will sacrifice everything
让布洛哈特上位
to get Brockhart into office,
而这就让康威变弱  容易失败
which makes Conway weak, ready to lose.
我以为你和我看法相同
I thought you saw what I saw.
确实
I did. I do.
我们完全同步  克莱尔
We're perfectly in sync, Claire.
最高法院基本任命流程是  当法院出现空缺  总统提名一个人选
然后参议院举行公开听证会  一般持续三到五天
然后参议院进行投票  如果被提名者获得多数票  就可以宣誓就职
历史上也出现过休会任命大法官
但休会任命的局限是  在参议院复会后  还是要进行任命投票
在最高法院大法官的任命投票上  民主党在控制参议院时
取消了原有的阻挠议事  允许51票简单多数即可过关
这种规则的更改  却让共和党占了便宜
在不久前特朗普提名大法官后  因为目前共和党控制了参议院
虽然民主党非常反对  但共和党仍靠简单多数投票让大法官上任了
在美国早期  现代政党系统还没有成型的时候
出现过正副总统分属不同党派的情况
亚当斯做总统时  副总统杰斐逊跟他不是一个党派
创立了共和党的林肯  出于选举策略的考虑  选了民主党杰克逊做副总统
根据法律  这种情况是可能出现的
因为一旦选举结果有争议  需要国会来投票选举总统时
总统是由众议院选举产生  而副总统是由参议院选举产生
这就可能出现正副总统不同党  但历史上没有发生过